peaks.com 2006-06-22

# American Skiing Company | Privacy Policy

| 

**American Skiing Company** **Internet Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the American Skiing Company ("ASC") and all ASC-owned resorts and subsidiaries with regard to information it collects. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, when this policy refers to the American Skiing Company, it refers to all ASC-owned resorts and and governs each of their web sites. For a list of all ASC-owned resorts, please click on [www.peaks.com](http://www.peaks.com/).

**About Our Privacy Policy**

American Skiing Company respects your privacy. Throughout our family of resorts, we will only collect, store and use the personal information we collect on our web sites for those purposes defined in this policy. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship and communication with you. Except as stated in this policy, we will not sell, rent or lease your personal information. At any time you may contact ASC or any of its resorts with any questions or concerns that you have about this policy.

**When Personal Information is Collected on Our Web site**

  * We may collect the personal information that you volunteer on registration, order, survey, sweepstakes entry, competition entry, or other forms, or by email.
  * We may collect personal information from your browser via Cookies, when you visit our web site and your browser interacts with our web site.
  * We may collect personal information when you make a purchase on our website.

**Use of Information Collected on our Website**

The information we collect on our website is used to develop better products, optimize your experience on our web sites and improve our communication with you so that we may maximize your ASC experience. We will always notify you, on the web page where you give us information and/or in the policy governing the contest, sweepstakes or special event or opportunity, if we intend to use your information differently than we have described in this privacy policy, as in the case of contests or sweepstakes. Please be sure to read these web pages or rules, as our use of the information collected there may vary from this Policy or from the policies that have governed previous contests, sweepstakes or other special event or opportunity.

We also use the information we collect online to support our off-line marketing activities, such as direct mail. The information we collect may also be shared with any American Skiing Company-owned resort or subsidiary, all of which have adopted the principles contained in this privacy policy.

American Skiing Company or any of its resorts, may, from time to time, contact you via email on behalf of business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, the communication will come to you from us - and will only be a part of a communication to which you have opted-in, such as a newsletter or snow report. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable online contact information (e-mail address or IP address) is not transferred to the third party.

**Information We Share With Others**

Except as stated in this policy, we will not sell, lease or rent your personal information to any third party. However, we may share your off-line contact information (name & address) with trusted partner companies who may use this information to send you direct mail concerning promotional or other opportunities on a limited basis. As you may elect not to receive on-line or _off-line_ communication from us, you may also elect not to receive off-line communication from our partner companies. See our opt-out instructions below.

We never give your email address or telephone number to third parties, including our partner companies.

We sometimes employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. For example, hosting our website and database, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links, analyzing data, etc. These third parties have access to personal information needed to perform these functions, but may not use it for other purposes and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

**Use of Information Collected After Sale or Merger**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy resorts, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). In the event that ASC or one of its resorts or subsidiaries is sold, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information could be one of the transferred assets.

**Disclosure**

In certain special cases, we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with ASC's rights, property or operations, other ASC site users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, a pending civil case, administrative investigation or investigation conducted by ASC. We shall have no obligation to inform you of our compliance with the law, including without limitation a response to a law enforcement request or a valid subpoena.

**Links**

Our web site may enable you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others through our online Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms. When you use these services, the information that you share may be collected by other visitors. We do not provide any type of security or protection for information that you provide in our Chat Rooms or on our Bulletin Boards. Information concerning the policies and procedures that govern each Bulletin Board and Chat Room is available on each site. We reserve the right to censor information that we deem to be distasteful, harmful or otherwise inappropriate on our Bulletin Boards and in our Chat Rooms.

Our web site also contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other web sites. We encourage you to note when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies listed on these (and all) third party sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on ASC web sites. If you choose to provide information on a third-party site, that information will be subject to that party's privacy policy. For instance, lodging reservations made through some of our web sites are made by WorldRes Inc. which is not a partner, affiliate or subsidiary of ASC. When you make a reservation at some of our resorts, you may leave that resort's web site and enter WorldRes' site. While you are on WorldRes' web site, WorldRes' privacy policy governs any and all information you choose to provide. We may receive personal information back from other sites that are linked to this site, such as WorldRes. Our use of information we receive from linked sites is governed by our Privacy Policy.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies from time-to-time to help you, for example, to navigate efficiently between secure and non-secure pages of our site; to participate in sweepstakes or monthly drawings; or to help us identify special interests that you may have and that enhance your experience on our web sites. "Cookies" are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use all of the features of our site, including purchasing tickets and other products online. We may track the web site you come from or go to. We may track what browser you use so as to send you pages appropriate for your browser. We may also collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. We may use this information for the operation of online services, to maintain quality of online services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of this website.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

**Tracking Tags**

American Skiing Company uses tracking tags such as pixels or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partners including DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and tracking tag technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to <http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>.

**Security**

ASC operates secure data networks protected by firewall and password protection. ASC has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every reasonable effort to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number from our system and/or cancel a pass product, user name or password and update our records accordingly.

**Review or Change your Information or Preferences**

You may ask us whether we are keeping personal information about you by sending an email, with your complete name and address to [databasemanager@ascresorts.com](mailto:databasemanager@ascresorts.com), or by sending postal mail to this address: Attn: Database Marketing Manager, American Skiing Company, P.O. Box 4552, Park City, Utah, 84060. We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal information that we keep about you within thirty days of your request, without charge. You may correct, amend or delete any of your information or change your preferences.

**Visitor Choice Opt-in/Opt-out Program**

**Opt in:** You may choose to receive promotional or marketing information from our resorts by going to [www.peaks.com/email.html](http://www.peaks.com/email.html) and selecting the resort(s) of your choice. ****

**Opt-out:** If you are receiving promotional or marketing information from us and no longer wish to receive such information, you may choose to opt-out or unsubscribe by going to [www.peaks.com/email.html](http://www.peaks.com/email.html) and selecting the resort(s) of your choice. ****or by sending an email to[databasemanager@ascresorts.com](mailto:databasemanager@ascresorts.com). Each time we contact you via email using your personal information, we will offer you an opportunity to opt-out or unsubscribe, either entirely or for specific purposes. Please note that our online subscription database is for email marketing programs only. To opt-out from all communications including direct mail, please change your preferences by sending an e-mail to [databasemanager@ascresorts.com](mailto:databasemanager@ascresorts.com) or by sending postal mail to Database Marketing Manager, American Skiing Company, P.O. Box 4552, Park City, Utah, 84060.

**Children's Privacy (Age 12 and Under)**

We are concerned about the safety of children and will comply, at all times, with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect e-mail subscription information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have e-mail subscription information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems as soon as we discover that it has been submitted it and we will not disclose it to third parties.

**Privacy Support**

If you would like more information regarding our use of your personal information, or you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Attn: Database Marketing Manager  
American Skiing Company  
P.O. Box 4552  
Park City, Utah, 84060

Or by email: [databasemanager@ascresorts.com](mailto:databasemanager@ascresorts.com)

**VERY IMPORTANT:** If you feel that a site using the ASC brands and/or logos has not posted an acceptable privacy policy, or is not following the privacy policy it has posted, please send us an email at [databasemanager@ascresorts.com](mailto:databasemanager@ascresorts.com). If appropriate, we may forward complaints to the appropriate third parties and help you follow up to ensure that your concerns are adequately handled. Of course, if any of these third party companies does not have a privacy policy that is acceptable to you, you should refrain from providing information until your concerns have been satisfactorily addressed.

**ASC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be posted to this page, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of any significant changes to this privacy policy. However, it is your responsibility to check this site for any such updates as you will be bound by them should you choose to visit our sites.**
